Hello. In this video we demonstrate
how to install the Attack Graph Generator.
We first enter the directory where the program is saved.
We then enter the command for starting the program.
The program has to run in sudo mode.
Once the program is started, it automatically
downloads and installs the needed third-party components
needed for the program to run properly.
The user should press Y and Enter couple of times
to allow the components to be installed on the host machine.
The installation process should last couple of minutes.
Some of the parts in this video are intentionally skipped,
in order to reduce waiting time.
Some of the third-party components include:
python, pip, docker, docker-compose, go,
clairctl, graphviz, pyyaml, networkx and the examples.
Once all of the third-party components are downloaded and installed,
the attack graph generation procedure is automatically initialized.
For a walkthrough of running the program, please watch the second video.
Thank you for your attention.