In this video we conduct a walktrough of the Attack Graph Generator.
The program is automatically initialized after the installation process.
First, topology parsing is performed.
Then, the docker images are built. This part should take some time.
Parts of this video are intentionally skipped, in order to reduce waiting time.
Postgres, Clair and Clairctl are pulled and started.
The images are pushed to Clair and analyzed for vulnerabilities.
We can notice that no vulnerabilities are detected for these images.
After the vulnerabilities are extracted, the attack graph generation is started.
The attack graph generation is finished.
No vulnerabilities were detected because Clair needs
some time to populate the database with known vulnerabilities.
We recommend waiting for couple of hours and starting the program again.
Now, let us see the folder structure.
The folder examples contains the Docker Compose systems.
Inside the javaee system, we can see the file called docker-compose.yml
This file describes the connections between different containers.
The config file contains the user-defined settings and
the precondition and postcondition rules
required for the attack graph generation process.
examples-results contains the produced files from the attack graph generation.
Here, we observe the resulting topology graph.
The attack graph is empty because Clair did not detect vulnerabilities.
The vulnerabilities report file generated by Clair.
This was a short summary of the attack graph generator setup and run.
For more information please refer to the README.md file and the comments.
Thank you for your attention.